UTC +3 pm@bvndls.com +79377700336 Kazan, Tatarstan

Personal Statement

I'm an IT Specialist experienced in Systems Operations and Customer Service Support. While I've mainly worked in support, I'm also proficient in DevOps, System Administration, and SRE roles. I'm committed to continuous learning. I prefer remote work but am open to hybrid or onsite roles in Kazan or Moscow.

Experience

SENIOR SUPPORT SPECIALIST, SOVCOMBANK TECHNOLOGIES; KAZAN, RUSSIA — 2021-2023

- · Provided support for car insurance, credit accounting, and cost optimization systems
- · Started, maintained, and presented a new project (Implementation of VR in a bank)
- · Improved internal processes by enhancing and adding documentation, refining feedback forms, and working on better inter-team communication
- · Assisted in content migration for two large sites during a redesign
- · Maintained project communication, hosted daily meetings
- · Automated processes using Python and Bash scripting:
 - 1. Mobile Cost Optimization data collection and processing, report generation
 - 2. <u>Health Insurance website</u> scraping data from the old website, migration, integrity checks
- · Trained 4 employees

SYSTEMS OPERATOR AND MAINTENANCE SPECIALIST, THE DEEP VR; KAZAN, RUSSIA — 2020-2021

- · Resolved a wide variety of hardware and software-related difficulties
- · Set up the equipment for the opening of a new location
- · Delivered customer support on how to use VR devices
- · Maintained and coordinated equipment purchases
- · Ensured the best experience possible

Education

Kazan National Research Technological University Incomplete Higher Education (2022), Secondary Professional Education (2018-2021). Thesis - "Application of Virtual Reality technologies for tourism development"

Skills

Soft skills: fast learning, analytical thinking, attention to detail, communication, conflict resolution, time management, technical writing skills and public speaking. Hard skills: Python and Bash scripting, web application development (HTML, CSS, JS), Linux, git, containerization (Docker CLI, Rancher, Portainer), monitoring (Zabbix, Grafana, Graylog), DBMS (MySQL, Oracle PL/SQL), Pyrus, Confluence, video editing (FCPX, Premiere Pro).

